Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-396. Wages
    - Wichita Terminal Association, Wichita, Kansas.1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 576, Folder 41)
    - Wichita Terminal Association, Wichita, Kansas.1956 Wage Movement (Box 576, Folder 42)
    - Wichita Terminal Association, Wichita, Kansas.1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 576, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 408-397. Wages
    - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Company. General, 1944-1955 (Box 576, Folder 44)
    - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 577, Folder 1)
    - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 2)
    - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-398. Wages
    - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau. General, 1943-1955 (Box 577, Folder 4)
    - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 577, Folder 5)
    - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 6)
    - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-399. Wages
    - Joint Agency National Stock Yards, East St. Louis, Illinois. General, 1945-1955 (Box 577, Folder 8)
    - Joint Agency National Stock Yards, East St. Louis, Illinois. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 577, Folder 9)
    - Joint Agency National Stock Yards, East St. Louis, Illinois. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 10)
    - Joint Agency National Stock Yards, East St. Louis, Illinois. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-400. Wages
    - New England Transportation Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 577, Folder 12)
    - New England Transportation Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-402. Wages
    - Eastern Canada Stevedoring Company. General, 1943-1955 (Box 577, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-403. Wages
    - Missouri Produce Yard, Kansas City, Missouri. General, 1954 (Box 577, Folder 15)
    - Missouri Produce Yard, Kansas City, Missouri. General, 1941-1953 (Box 577, Folder 16)
    - Missouri Produce Yard, Kansas City, Missouri. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 577, Folder 17)
    - Missouri Produce Yard, Kansas City, Missouri. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 18)
    - Missouri Produce Yard, Kansas City, Missouri. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-404. Wages
    - Manistee and North Eastern Railway Company. General, 1948-1959 (Box 577, Folder 20)
    - Manistee and North Eastern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 21)
    - Manistee and North Eastern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-405. Wages
    - Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston, Texas. General, 1944-1959 (Box 577, Folder 23)
    - Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston, Texas. Mediation Case No. A-1938, 1944-1945 (Box 577, Folder 24)
    - Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston, Texas. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 25)
    - Union Passenger Depot Company of Galveston, Texas. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-406. Wages
    - Rock Island Motor Transit Company. General, 1944-1955 (Box 577, Folder 27)
    - Rock Island Motor Transit Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 577, Folder 28)
    - Rock Island Motor Transit Company. 1956 Wage Movement. Health and Welfare, 1956-1958 (Box 577, Folder 29)
      1956 -58.
  - Sub-Series 408-408. Wages
    - Patapsco and Back Rivers Railroad Company. General, 1945-1956 (Box 577, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-409. Wages
    - Joint Railway Agency, South St. Paul, Minnesota. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 577, Folder 31)
    - Joint Railway Agency, South St. Paul, Minnesota. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 577, Folder 32)
    - Joint Railway Agency, South St. Paul, Minnesota. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-410. Wages
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. General, 1951-1961 (Box 577, Folder 34)
      March 1951-61.
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. General, 1947-1951 (Box 577, Folder 35)
      1947-March 1951.
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-5510. Rights of Employees in the Event of Carrier Abandonment of Facilities; Request for Pay Increase, 1957 (Box 577, Folder 36)
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 37)
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-5214, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 38)
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-3848, 1951-1952 (Box 577, Folder 39)
    - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railway Company. 40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 577, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 408-411. Wages
    - Tremont and Gulf Railway. General, 1945-1955 (Box 577, Folder 41)
    - Tremont and Gulf Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 577, Folder 42)
    - Tremont and Gulf Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 577, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 408-412. Wages
    - Rio Grande Motor Way, Inc. General, 1945-1954 (Box 577, Folder 44)
    - Rio Grande Motor Way, Inc. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 408-413. Wages
    - Trailways Bus Depot, St. Louis, Missouri.1956 Wage Movement (Box 577, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 408-414. Wages
    - Winston-Salem Terminal Company, Winston-Salem, North Carolina. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7067, 1963-1965 (Box 577, Folder 47)
    - Winston-Salem Terminal Company, Winston-Salem, North Carolina. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 578, Folder 1)
    - Winston-Salem Terminal Company, Winston-Salem, North Carolina. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 578, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 408-416. Wages
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Wage Adjustment of 25 Cents per Hour, Employees in Puerto Rico, 1953-1956 (Box 578, Folder 3)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-4674, 1954-1955 (Box 578, Folder 4)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3903, 1951-1952 (Box 578, Folder 5)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3983, 1952 (Box 578, Folder 6)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-5832, 1958-1959 (Box 578, Folder 7)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-6130. Proposal for Increase in Rates of Pay, 1959-1961 (Box 578, Folder 8)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3287, 1949-1950 (Box 578, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-419. Wages
    - Oakland Terminal Railway, Oakland, California. General, 1946-1954 (Box 578, Folder 10)
    - Oakland Terminal Railway, Oakland, California.1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 578, Folder 11)
    - Oakland Terminal Railway, Oakland, California.1956 Wage Movement (Box 578, Folder 12)
    - Oakland Terminal Railway, Oakland, California.1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 578, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-420. Wages
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc. General, 1946-1952 (Box 578, Folder 14)
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3868, 1951-1952 (Box 578, Folder 15)
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-1941, 1948 (Box 578, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-421. Wages
    - Sand Springs Railway. General, 1945-1954 (Box 578, Folder 17)
    - Sand Springs Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 578, Folder 18)
    - Sand Springs Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 578, Folder 19)
    - Sand Springs Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 578, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-422. Wages
    - Transcontinental Bus System. Continental Dixie Lines. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 578, Folder 21)
    - Transcontinental Bus System. Continental Dixie Lines. Agreement, 1946 (Box 578, Folder 22)
      1946 December 15
  - Sub-Series 408-425. Wages
    - Niagara, St. Catherines and Toronto Railway. General, 1954 (Box 578, Folder 23)
    - Niagara, St. Catherines and Toronto Railway. General, 1948-1954 (Box 578, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-426. Wages
    - Union Bus Station of Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. General, 1946-1954 (Box 578, Folder 25)
    - Union Bus Station of Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 578, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-427. Wages
    - Freight Forwarding Companies. ABC Freight Forwarding Company: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, Chicago, Illinois. National Carloading Corporation: Chicago and Northwestern Railway, Chicago, Illinois. Universal Carloading and Distributing Company: Lehigh Valle, 1946-1955 (Box 578, Folder 27)
    - Freight Forwarding Companies. ABC Freight Forwarding Company: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, Chicago, Illinois. National Carloading Corporation: Chicago and Northwestern Railway, Chicago, Illinois. Universal Carloading and Distributing Company: Lehigh Valle, 1963-1965 (Box 578, Folder 28)
    - Freight Forwarding Companies. ABC Freight Forwarding Company: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, Chicago, Illinois. National Carloading Corporation: Chicago and Northwestern Railway, Chicago, Illinois. Universal Carloading and Distributing Company: Lehigh Valle, 1955-1956 (Box 578, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-428. Wages
    - Canadian Interior Navigation and Stevedoring Companies. General, 1950-1952 (Box 578, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-429. Wages
    - Springmeier Shipping Company, Inc. 1961 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 578, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-430. Wages
    - New York Central Railroad Grain Elevators, New York, New York and Weehawken, New Jersey. General, 1931-1950 (Box 578, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-436. Wages
    - Air Transport Industry. General, 1948-1956 (Box 578, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-437. Wages
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. General, 1946-1951 (Box 578, Folder 34)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. General, 1952-1960 (Box 579, Folder 1)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3898, 1952 (Box 579, Folder 2)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3708, 1951 (Box 579, Folder 3)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-5859. Revision of Agreement Proposed by Employer, 1958-1963 (Box 579, Folder 4)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-4296. Employees' Exhibits, 1953-1954 (Box 579, Folder 5)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-4296, 1953 (Box 579, Folder 6)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-5859. Employees' Exhibits, 1959 (Box 579, Folder 7-12)
      1959 February
  - Sub-Series 408-438. Wages
    - Capital Airlines. General, 1950-1955 (Box 579, Folder 13)
    - Capital Airlines. Mediation Case No. A-6037, 1959 (Box 579, Folder 14)
    - Capital Airlines. Mediation Case No. A-4094, 1952-1953 (Box 579, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-441. Wages
    - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 579, Folder 16)
    - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 17)
    - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-447. Wages
    - Trans-World Airlines. General, 1947-1949 (Box 579, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-452. Wages
    - Georgia Southern and Florida Railway. General, 1950-1955 (Box 579, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-456. Wages
    - Natchez and Southern Railway Company. General, 1950-1955 (Box 579, Folder 21)
    - Natchez and Southern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 579, Folder 22)
    - Natchez and Southern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 23)
    - Natchez and Southern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 579, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-458. Wages
    - River Terminal Railway Company. General, 1952-1955 (Box 579, Folder 25)
    - River Terminal Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 579, Folder 26)
    - River Terminal Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 27)
    - River Terminal Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-459. Wages
    - High Point, Randleman, Asheboro and Southern Railroad Company. High Point, Thomasville and Denton Railroad Company. General, 1950 (Box 579, Folder 29)
    - High Point, Randleman, Asheboro and Southern Railroad Company. High Point, Thomasville and Denton Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-465. Wages
    - Pullman Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 579, Folder 31)
    - Pullman Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 579, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-468. Wages
    - Canadian Grain Elevators. General, 1950-1955 (Box 579, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-477. Wages
    - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad Company. General, 1954-1959 (Box 580, Folder 1)
    - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad Company. General, 1946-1953 (Box 580, Folder 2)
    - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 580, Folder 3)
    - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 580, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-487. Wages
    - Reading Transportation Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 580, Folder 5)
    - Reading Transportation Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 580, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-488. Wages
    - Western Air Lines, Inc. General, 1950 (Box 580, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-490. Wages
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3315. Arbitration No. 134. Wage Increase Proposal. Employees' Exhibits, 1950 (Box 580, Folder 8-14)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3315. Arbitration No. 134. Wage Increase Proposal, 1949-1950 (Box 580, Folder 15)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3315. Arbitration No. 134. Wage Increase Proposal. Proceedings. Volume 1, 1950 (Box 580, Folder 16)
      May 1-3, 1950.
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3315. Arbitration No. 134. Wage Increase Proposal. Proceedings. Volume 2, 1950 (Box 580, Folder 17)
      May 4-9, 1950.
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3315. Arbitration No. 134. Wage Increase Proposal. Proceedings. Volume 3, 1950 (Box 580, Folder 18)
      May 10-11, 1950.
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-4044, 1952-1953 (Box 580, Folder 19)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-2641. Employers' Exhibits, 1948 (Box 581, Folder 1)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-2641. Brotherhood Exhibits, 1948 (Box 581, Folder 2)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-2641, 1948-1950 (Box 581, Folder 3)
    - Mid-Continent Air Lines. Mediation Case No. A-3654, 1947-1952 (Box 581, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-492. Wages
    - Salt Lake Union Stock Yards Operating Company.1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 581, Folder 5)
    - Salt Lake Union Stock Yards Operating Company.1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 6)
    - Salt Lake Union Stock Yards Operating Company.1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 7)
    - Salt Lake Union Stock Yards Operating Company.40-Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 581, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-497. Wages
    - Union Bus Depot, Peoria, Illinois. General, 1947-1955 (Box 581, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-499. Wages
    - Bamberger Railroad Company. Salt Lake Terminal Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. General, 1941-1959 (Box 581, Folder 10)
    - Bamberger Railroad Company. Salt Lake Terminal Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 581, Folder 11)
    - Bamberger Railroad Company. Salt Lake Terminal Company, Salt Lake City, Utah. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-503. Wages
    - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company. General, 1947-1950 (Box 581, Folder 13)
    - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 581, Folder 14)
    - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-4683, 1954-1956 (Box 581, Folder 15)
    - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 16)
    - Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-504. Wages
    - Trailways Union Bus Depot, Kansas City, Missouri. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-506. Wages
    - Southern Pacific Railway, Hospital Department.1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-507. Wages
    - Central Railroad of Pennsylvania. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-510. Wages
    - American Overseas Airlines. General, 1949-1950 (Box 581, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-512. Wages
    - Milwaukee-Kansas City Southern Joint Agency. General, 1947-1953 (Box 581, Folder 22)
    - Milwaukee-Kansas City Southern Joint Agency. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 23)
    - Milwaukee-Kansas City Southern Joint Agency. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-513. Wages
    - Missouri Pacific Transportation Company, Memphis, Tennessee. General, 1947-1950 (Box 581, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-514. Wages
    - Fort Smith Bus Terminal, Fort Smith, Arkansas.1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-515. Wages
    - Little Rock Bus Depot, Little Rock, Arkansas. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-517. Wages
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-5680, 1957-1958 (Box 581, Folder 28)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-6204. Pay Increase and Union Security, 1960 (Box 581, Folder 29)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-5060, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 30)
      1955-May 3, 1956.
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-4028, 1952-1953 (Box 581, Folder 31)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3452, 1949-1950 (Box 581, Folder 32)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-3542, 1950 (Box 581, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-519. Wages
    - New Jersey and New York Railroad. General, 1945-1954 (Box 581, Folder 34)
    - New Jersey and New York Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 581, Folder 35)
    - New Jersey and New York Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 581, Folder 36)
    - New Jersey and New York Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 408-526. Wages
    - Keokuk Union Depot, Keokuk, Iowa. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 581, Folder 38)
    - Keokuk Union Depot, Keokuk, Iowa. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 39)
    - Keokuk Union Depot, Keokuk, Iowa. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 408-537. Wages
    - Manufacturers Junction Railway Company. General, 1949-1954 (Box 581, Folder 41)
    - Manufacturers Junction Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 581, Folder 42)
    - Manufacturers Junction Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 581, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 408-552. Wages
    - Terminal Railway of Alabama State Docks, Mobile, Alabama. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 581, Folder 44)
    - Terminal Railway of Alabama State Docks, Mobile, Alabama. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 45)
    - Terminal Railway of Alabama State Docks, Mobile, Alabama. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 408-567. Wages
    - Newburgh and South Shore Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 581, Folder 47)
    - Newburgh and South Shore Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 408-576. Wages
    - Illinois Northern Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 49)
    - Illinois Northern Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 408-594. Wages
    - Canadian National Railways, Central Region. Canadian National Railway Elevator, Portland, Maine. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 51)
    - Canadian National Railways, Central Region. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 581, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 408-608. Wages
    - South Georgia Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 582, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 408-613. Wages
    - Montour Railroad. General, 1948-1954 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    - Montour Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 582, Folder 3)
    - Montour Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    - Montour Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-614. Wages
    - Chicago Railways' Hotel Ticket Offices. General, 1947-1954 (Box 582, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Railways' Hotel Ticket Offices. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1960 (Box 582, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-616. Wages
    - National Air Terminal Service Company, Inc. General, 1948-1951 (Box 582, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-618. Wages
    - Old Point Comfort Joint Agency. General, 1946-1950 (Box 582, Folder 9)
      1946-50.
  - Sub-Series 408-621. Wages
    - Ahnapee and Western Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 582, Folder 10)
    - Ahnapee and Western Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 11)
    - Ahnapee and Western Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement. Mediation Case No. A-5469, 1956-1959 (Box 582, Folder 12)
      1956-59.
  - Sub-Series 408-627. Wages
    - Youngstown and Southern Railway Company. General, 1948-1954 (Box 582, Folder 13)
      1948-54.
    - Youngstown and Southern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 582, Folder 14)
    - Youngstown and Southern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 582, Folder 15)
      1956-57.
    - Youngstown and Southern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 16)
      1955-56.
  - Sub-Series 408-628. Wages
    - Oklahoma City Stock Yards Agency. General, 1945-1955 (Box 582, Folder 17)
      1945-55.
    - Oklahoma City Stock Yards Agency. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 582, Folder 18)
      1963-65.
    - Oklahoma City Stock Yards Agency. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 19)
    - Oklahoma City Stock Yards Agency. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-631. Wages
    - Air Cargo, Inc. General, 1954 (Box 582, Folder 21)
    - Air Cargo, Inc. Mediation Cases Nos. A-2891 and A-3461, 1948-1950 (Box 582, Folder 22)
      1948-50.
  - Sub-Series 408-636. Wages
    - Chicago, West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company. General, 1948-1958 (Box 582, Folder 23)
      1948-58.
    - Chicago, West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 582, Folder 24)
    - Chicago, West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 25)
    - Chicago, West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-637. Wages
    - Trans-Continental Bus System, Inc. General, 1948-1955 (Box 582, Folder 27)
      1948-55.
    - Trans-Continental Bus System, Inc. Continental Central Lines. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-638. Wages
    - Carolina and Northwestern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7066, 1963-1965 (Box 582, Folder 29)
    - Carolina and Northwestern Railway Company. Blue Ridge Railway Company. Danville and Western Railway Company. High Point, Randleman, Asheboro and Southern Railroad Company. Yadkin Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 30)
    - Carolina and Northwestern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-639. Wages
    - Blue Ridge Railroad. General, 1949-1959 (Box 582, Folder 32)
      1949-59.
    - Blue Ridge Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-642. Wages
    - Lexington Union Station, Lexington, Kentucky. General, 1948-1959 (Box 582, Folder 34)
      1948-59.